# **ABOUT ME**

Studying in a computer engineering school, I am interested in software development and engineering. I would like to get experience in the phases and methodologies of the development process. I am enthusiatic about technology products that deliver new solutions.

# **CONTACTS**

**E-mail**: sami.benamar@viacesi.fr **Linkedin**: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sami-benamar/

## **LANGUAGES**

- French (Native)
- English
- German

# **COMPUTER SKILLS**

- PHP
- NodeJS
- MySQL
- HTML/CSS
- Javascript
- C++/C#
- Java
- Python
- Arduino
- · Networking base
- OPCUA
- Universal Robot
- Sensopart

#### **HOBBIES**

- Tennis, ranked 32 practiced 3 years
- School trips to Dublin in 2014 and Budapest in 2018
- Programming, website creation for 5 years

# **SAMI BENAMAR**

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

#### **B&S Robsim**

Apprenticeship 2021-2024

- Computer software development.
- Robotic and HMI programming in the industrial world.

#### **B&S Robsim**

Internship scheduled from April 6, 2021 to July 30, 2021

 Development of a Cobot robot capable of palletizing, handling and screwing. It is intended to help areas where the pace slows down.

#### **B&S Robsim**

Developer from August 3, 2020 to September 11, 2020

- Programming to automate a miniature robotic line.
- Development of a mobile application to remotely control the robotic line.

#### Creation of programs and websites

2016 - 2020

- Development of various websites.
- Development of a stock management and invoicing software for Alsace Media Center.

### **EDUCATION**

## **CESI School of Engineering Strasbourg**

Apprenticeship 2021-2024

- Engineering training in the field of computer science.
- Apprenticeship in the company B&S Robsim.

#### **CESI School of Engineering Strasbourg**

Integrated preparation 2019-2021

- Engineer training in the field of computer science.
- President of the Bureau Des Sports association.

#### **High School Heinrich-Nessel**

2016-2019

 Scientific baccalaureate, engineering science option, mathematics speciality, European section English. Mention Bien.